-乔伊  试镜怎么样  -不可思议
- Hey Joey, how'd the audition go? - Incredible!
你们绝对不会相信
I met the director this time and
-我这回碰到了哪位导演  -谁呀
- you'll never believe who it was. - Who?
好  我给你们一个提示  沃伦·比提
All right. I'll give you one hint. Warren Beatty.
只是有件事  或许会成为问题
Yeah, there's just one thing that might be kind've a problem.
我  必须要吻一个男人
See, I, uh, had to kiss this guy.
因为他帅呆了吗
'Cause he was just so darn cute.
不  那是试镜的一部分
No, as part of the audition.
我试镜的角色  是男主角要亲的男人
See, I'm up for this part of this guy, who the main guy kisses.
你是个演员  那你就认命放嘴去吻吧
Well, hey. You're an actor, I say you just suck it up and do it.
直接吻也行
Or you just do it.
我吻了  我很专业
I did do it, I'm a professional.
那有什么问题
Then what's the problem?
我试镜完之后  比提先生过来跟我说
See after the scene, Mr. Beatty comes up to me and says
好演技  烂吻技
'good actor, bad kisser'.
你们相信吗  我  吻技很烂
Can you believe that, me not a good kisser,
那就好像是说
that's like,
特丽莎修女不是个好修女一样
like Mother Theresa, not a good mother.
好了  谁在乎他怎么想
Well, come on, who cares what that guy thinks.
沃伦·比提懂什么叫做接吻
What does Warren Beatty know about kissing.
你经纪人怎么说
Hey, what did your agent say?
接吻这回事绝对是个问题
Yep, this kiss thing is defiantly a problem,
比提先生星期一要再看一次
Mr. Beatty wants to see it again on Monday.
我得搞清楚我哪里做错了
Man, I gotta figure out what I'm doing wrong.
你们哪个女的先来吻我一下
Oh, okay, one of you girls come over here and kiss me.
你休想
What, forget it!
说得好
Yeah, right.
不要这样嘛  我需要帮忙啊
Come on, I need your help here.
好吧我来
All right. I'll do it,
我以前亲过他  再亲一次也无妨
I kissed him before I can do it again.
看到没  这才叫朋友
You see this, this is a friend.
开始
Uh-huh, let's go.
等等  香口胶
Oh, wait I have gum.
好了
Okay.
非常好  温柔而有力
Good, very good, firm but tender.
我会推荐给朋友
I'd recommend you to a friend.
那我就不知道问题出在哪里了
Then I don't know what it is. What's the problem?
乔伊  或许你是不习惯亲男人罢了
Joey, you know, maybe your just not used to kissing men,
或许你只是有点紧张
maybe you just tensed up a little bit,
也许你要克服这一点
maybe that's what you need to work on.
对  有道理
Yeah, that makes sense.
除非我死了
Over my dead body!
我会用他的尸体来当挡箭牌
And I'll be using his dead body as a shield.
出来吧亲爱的  你听我说  你很美
Come on out, honey! I'm telling you look good!
跟她说她很美...
Tell her she looks good, tell her she looks good.
老天啊
Oh my God,
你好美哦
you look so good!
真不敢相信我得在两百人面前步上红毯
I can not believe I have to walk down the aisle in front of 200 people
打扮得却像一瓶止吐糖浆
looking like something you drink when your nauseous.
那就别去啊  反正我不懂干嘛非去不可
So don't, I don't see why we have to go to this thing anyway,
这是你前未婚夫的婚礼
it's your ex-fiance's wedding.
因为我答应了明蒂会去
Because I promised Mindy I would.
你也答应过巴瑞  要嫁给他的
Yeah, well you promised Barry, you'd marry him.
各位  我必须去  我是伴娘
Look you guys, I have to go, I'm the Maid-of-Honor.
我只是需要再跟这些人  共聚一堂
And besides you know what I just need to be in a room again
而不会觉得不安
with these people and feel good about myself.
有人还穿着昨天晚上的衣服
Ooh-oh! Someone's wearing the same clothes they had on last night.
有人有什么艳遇吗
Someone get a little action?
或许吧
I may have.
花花公子
Woo-hoo, stuud!
她长的什么样
What's she look like?
我们还没见过面
Well, we haven't exactly met,
只是在网上谈了一整夜而已
we just stayed up all night talking on the internet.
呆子
Woo-hoo, geeek!
我喜欢她  我真的很喜欢她
I like this girl, okay, I seriously like this girl,
你们也知道  有时我会挖苦别人来保护自己
you now how sometimes I tend get a little defended and quipy...
少来了
Get out!
不会啦
Nooo! Please!
她直接批评我
Well she totally called me on it, okay.
她说"少来了  正经一点"
She said, 'cut it out, get real',
我照办了
and I did.
哇  那是什么样子
Wow! What's that like?
像这样  我  不开玩笑
It's like this, me, no jokes.
好了  别这样  你吓死我了
All right, stop it, you're freaking me out.
是呀  我不喜欢你这样
Oh, yeah, I don't like you this way.
好吧  咱们待会儿见了
All right, I'll see you guys later.
-拜拜  理查德  -拜拜
- Bye, Richard. - Bye bye.
拜  亲爱的  我爱你
Bye sweetie,  I love you.
我也爱你
I love you, too.
我觉得我男朋友好棒哦
I think my boyfriend ever so dreamy,
不知道我们的婚礼会是什么样子
I wonder what our wedding's gonna be like.
你在胡扯什么  什么婚礼
What are you talking about? What wedding?
少来了  你们从没谈过吗
Come on, like you never talk about that.
从来都没有
Nooo! Never!
我们很珍惜现在所拥有的
I mean, we're living in the moment.
就这么一次不去想  "将来会怎么样"
God, it is so nice for once to not have to get all
感觉真是太好了
hung up on 'Where is this going?'
你怕问他吗
Afraid to ask him?
怕得不能再怕了
Could not be more terrified.
我认为你应该认真考虑下  结婚这件事情
Well, I think you should seriously consider the marriage thing,
再给瑞秋一次  扮成口香糖公主的机会
give Rachel another chance to dress up like Princess Bubble Yum.
小本在哪里  他在这里
Where's Benny? There he is!
Where's Benny, there he is.
说不定这就是宝宝学说话的原因
You know that's probably why babies learn to talk,
好告诉大人们"够了"
so they can tell grown ups to cut it out.
我有个问题想要问你
Hey, you know I got a question for ya.
只是件小事啦  没有压力的
Just a little thing, no pressure.
问吧
Okay.
你有想过将来吗
Did you ever, uh, like, think about the future?
当然有
Sure I do.
是吗  将来有我吗
Yeah, am I in it?
亲爱的  你就是我的将来
Honey, you are in it.
天啊  你就要有艳福了
Oh God, you are about to get sooo lucky.
是嘛
Oh, yeah!
继续说
Keep talkin'.
有时我会想卖掉我的诊所
Well, uh, sometimes I think about selling my practice,
我们搬到法国去  做法国吐司
we could move to France, make French toast.
那么  我们在法国
Okay, so, uh, we're in France,
我们做吐司
and we're making the toast.
你的幻想中  墙角有没有小小的摇篮
Do you see a little bassinet in the corner?
猎犬吗
Like a hound?
不是猎狗  是摇篮
Not a basset, a bassinet.
你真的需要摇篮吗
You really need the bassinet?
否则宝宝会从狗身上掉下来呀
Well, I just think the baby would keep falling off the dog.
你没有幻想过我们有小孩吗
Do you, uh, do you , do you not see kids in our future.
我爱孩子
Oh, hey. I love children,
我也有孩子
I have children.
但我不想在我七十岁  孩子上大学时
I just don't want to be 70 when our kids go off to college,
我们的二人世界才开始
and our lives can finally start.
我现在就需要你
Look I want you, now.
太棒了
That's Great.
我们现在不需要谈这个
You know we don't need to talk about this now.
真的  我是说这是好久好久以后的事
Really, I mean this is, is so way, way, way, in the future,
这是"未来水世界"
I'm talkin' hovercrafts and
"人猿星球"的事
apes taking over the planet.
来嘛  钱德勒  我好想争取到这个角色
Come on, Chandler, I want this part soo much.
一吻就好  我不会到处说的
Just one kiss, I won't tell anyone.
乔伊  不就是不
Joey, no means no!
对不起  我们没有你的羊
I'm sorry we, we don't have your sheep.
瑞秋  我觉得你好可爱
Aww, Rach, I think you look cute.
而你  你...我真想咬你一口
And you, uh, you, you I could eat with a spoon.
离我远一点  我说了不行
Get away from me I said no!
理查德按了门铃  他在楼下等
Richard buzzed. He's waiting downstairs.
理查德来了  我该下去跟他说再见
Oh, Richard's here. I should run down say good bye to him.
拜拜
Bye.
祝一切顺利
Bye, good luck.
跟你那个电脑妞进展如何了
So how's your date with your cyberchick going.
那是什么
Ooh, hey, what is all that .
是古根汉美术馆的网址
Oh, it's a website, it's the, uh, the Guggenheim museum.
她喜欢艺术  而我喜欢怪字
See, she likes art, and I like funny words.
她说"HH"是什么意思
What does she mean by HH?
那就表示我们在牵手了
It means we're holding hands.
你真是太可爱了
Are you the cutest?
我想你说对了
I'm afraid I might just be.
我觉得这样很棒  你这么喜欢这个人
You know, what I think is so great that you are totally into this person
可是她可能已经九十岁了
and yet for all you know she could be like 90 years old,
或者是有两个头  或者可能是个男人
or have two heads, or. It could be a guy.
她不是男的  好吗  我知道她不是
Okay, it's not a guy, all right, I know her.
有可能是个大猛汉哦
It could be like a big giant guy.
我就差这么一点了
Man, I got this close to him
却被莫妮卡从背后踹了
and Monica kneed me in the back.
怎么了
What's going on?
我们正在猜  钱德勒的女友是不是女的
We were just wondering if Chandler's girlfriend is a girl.
那问她会活多久就可以了
Oh, well. Just ask her how long she's gonna live.
女人比男人长寿
Women live longer than men.
你还真是笨得到家了
How do you not fall down more?
你问她现在用什么方法避孕
Okay, ask her 'What is her current method of birth control?'
好吧
All right.
"我丈夫跟他的秘书有婚外情"
"My husband is sleeping with his secretary."
她结婚了
She's married!
至少我们知道她是个女的
Well at least we know she's a woman.
我真不敢相信她结婚了
I can't believe she's married.
老兄  真遗憾
Aw, man I'm sorry.
你心里一定很难受吧
This must be very tough for ya, huh .
我那天看到一篇文章说
So, I read this article the other day
不应该在婚礼上丢米庆祝
that says you're not supposed to throw rice at weddings,
因为鸽子吃了会死掉
because when pigeons eat rice it kills them.
难怪寿司店里都看不到鸽子
Oh, that's why you never see pigeons at sushi bars.
你瞧  我们很开心
See, we're having fun.
是啊
Oh, absolutely.
我根本连想都不想
Yeah, you know I'm not even thinking about that thing
我们不要去想的那件事
that we're not supposed to think about.
我也没想
Neither am I.
你还好吗
Are you all right?
我去上洗手间的时候
Yeah, when I was in the bathroom
看到我结婚时  爬出去的那扇窗子
I saw the window that I crawled out of at my wedding, and God,
然后我开始想  我不该来的
I just started thinking that I shouldn't be here, you know I shouldn't,
大家会打量我  评判我
people are going to be looking at me and judging me and,
然后就想到上一次的事
and thinking about the last time.
亲爱的  你不会有事的
Sweetie, it's be gonna okay, all right.
这是场婚礼  通常大家都只会注意新娘子
It's a wedding, generally people focus on the bride.
天啊  我知道你说得对
God I know, you're right.
好了  大家看着我
All rightie, everybody look at me.
很好  时间到了
Good. All right, its time.
伴娘跟招待  排成两列  谢谢
Bridesmaids and ushers let's see two lines, thank you.
咱们婚礼后见了
Okay, I'll see you after the thing.
祝好运
Okay, good luck.
谢谢
Thank you, Okay.
开始吧
Okay.
你为什么不告诉我啊
Why the hell didn't you tell me!
对不起  我该怎么做
I'm sorry. What was I supposed to do
难不成站起来大叫
stand up and shout
"瑞秋  你的屁股露出来了"
'Hey, Rachel, your butt is showing!'
天啊  真是丢脸丢到家了
Oh my God this is so humiliating.
我想唯一比这个还要丢脸的
I think the only thing that tops that was, was,
就是我初三时
was when I was in the eight grade and I had to sing
在全校面前唱  《古巴卡巴那》那次了
the Copa Cabana in front of the entire school.
我大概没唱两句就逃之夭夭了
I think I got about two lines into it before I ran and freaked out.
天啊  我悲惨的人生再现眼前
Oh my God, my entire life is flashing before my eyes.
瑞秋  听着  我记得  没那么糟的
Rach, hey look, I remember that, it wasn't so bad.
罗斯  你不用说好话了
Oh Ross, would you stop,
你已经追到我了
you got me, I'm dating you.
瑞秋
Rachel!
温伯格先生  温伯格太太  你们好
Oh hi, Mr. Weinberg, hi Mrs. Weinberg.
很高兴又看到你了  亲爱的
It's so wonderful to see you again, my dear,
老实说  我没想到会看到那么多
in fact I hardly expected to see so much.
你说你什么都没看到的
You told me you didn't see anything.
我说过很多话
I tell ya a lot things!
真高兴又看到你出来走动了  亲爱的
Well it's wonderful to have you up and about, again, dear.
好好保重
Stay well.
类似刚刚那种话
Okay, now that is the third time
我今天已经听到三次了
someone has said something like that to me today.
瑞秋  瑞秋
Rach, Rach.
天啊  我结婚了
Oh my God, I'm married!
我知道
I know.
我是巴瑞·亨特"连字符"法伯医生太太了
I'm Mrs. Dr. Barry Hunter hyphen Farber.
我真为你骄傲  明蒂
Oh honey, I'm so proud of you, Min.
明蒂  瑞秋
Min. Oh Rach,
你还在啊  我们婚礼的这个时候
you're still here, at our wedding,
大家已经在打包剩菜了
they were packing up the chopped liver about now.
是呀  我喜欢那个故事
Yeah, I love that story.
我有个问题要问你们
Um, I got a question for you guys.
为什么大家一直说  高兴看到我出来走动了
Why do people keep saying that is good to see me up and about?
在你逃婚之后
Well uh, after you ran out on your wedding,
巴瑞的父母告诉大家说  你疯了
Barry's parents told people that you were sort of....insane.
疯了
Insane!
梅毒引起的
From the syphilis.
什么
What?!
那他们该怎么说
Yeah, what are they gonna say
你不再爱我了吗  少来了
you didn't love me anymore. Come on.
安琪拉  我是乔伊·崔比安尼
Angela? Joey Tribiani.
你今晚做什么
Listen, what are you doing tonight.
我知道你在跟他交往
I know you're seeing that guy
我在想或许你可以带上他
I was thinking maybe you could bring him.....
喂  喂
Hello? Hello?
你还不回答她吗
Aren't you gonna answer her,
她已经发了十次消息过来了
that's like the tenth bing-bong message she sent.
她想知道怎么了
She wants to know what's wrong?
怎么了  你结婚了  这就是怎么了
What's wrong? What's wrong? You're married that's what's wrong.
天啊
Oh, my.
怎么了
What?
她想要跟你见面
She wants to meet you in person.
菲比  我也想见她本人
Hey, look, Phoebe I wanted to meet her in person too, okay,
但她结婚了  她有一个丈夫
but she's married, she has a husband.
如果这个丈夫不适合她  你才适合她呢
What if the husband person is the wrong guy, and you are the right guy.
这种机会不是常有的
I mean you don't get chances like this all the time,
如果你现在不见她
if you don't meet her now,
八十岁时  会气得踢自己的屁股
you're gonna be kicking yourself when your 80,
那可是高难度动作  你会折断髋骨的
which is hard to do, and that's how you break a hip.
好吧  我见她
Okay, I'll do it!
太棒了
Oh, yeah! Okay! Great!
穿上鞋子然后走出去见她吧
Go, man, go put on your shoes, and, and march out there and meet her!
不  等等  你必须先洗个澡
Oh, wait, no, no you have to take a shower, 'cause, eww.
不  先回答  先回答她的问题
No, you have to answer her, answer her first.
不  你先煮咖啡  太大压力了
No, no, you know what make some coffee 'cause its too much.
好了  拜托再来一次嘛
Okay, one more, please.
我这次会丢进去的
Come on, I'm gonna get it in this time, I will.
好吧  最后一次
Okay, last chance.
对不起  又打到你了
Again, I'm sorry.
知道吗  或许我不需要有孩子
You know what, maybe I don't need to have children.
我以为我需要  只是因为社会的问题
You know maybe I just think I do because that is what society,
我是指我妈
and by that I mean my mom,
她一直让我相信我...
has always convinced me that I...
我需要  我必须要有小孩
I do, I have to have children,
对不起  我必须要
I'm sorry, I just do.
请大家注意
Yo! Can I have your attention, please,
伴郎要敬酒了
Best Man, making a toast here.
谢谢
Thank you.
我记得巴瑞第一次跟瑞秋约会回来后的情景
I remember when Barry got home from his first date with Rachel...
怎么啦
What?!
你没有换乐队  却要我换祝酒词吗
you hired the same band I can't use the same speech.
谢谢  非常感谢
Thank you, thank you very much.
总之  祝你们白头偕老  幸福一辈子
Anyway, I wish you both a wonderful life together.
还有瑞秋
And Rachel...
什么
What.
不  我很认真的
No, no, no now in all seriousness,
没有多少女人有胆量  今晚回来这里
it's not a lot of women would've had the guts to come back here tonight,
而且还敢露屁股回来的  那就更少了
and even fewer, who would do it with their asses hanging out!
我想补充几句
Uh, I like to, uh, to add something to that...
为什么要补充...
Why are you adding, why are you adding, why are you adding?
你们大半都不认识我
Most of you don't know me,
我是瑞秋的男朋友
I'm Rachel's boyfriend.
老天
Oh dear God.
我叫罗斯  我想说
Ross, uh and uh, I'd just like to say
瑞秋真的是鼓足了勇气  今晚来到这里
that it did take a lot of courage for Rachel to come here tonight.
而且  我想澄清
And, uh, just for the record
瑞秋并不是因为得了梅毒才逃婚的
she did not run out on Barry because she had syphilis.
搞什么  我可没开玩笑
What are you doing I'm serious.
她离开巴瑞的原因  其实很简单
Uh, the reason she walked out on, on Barry is simply that
她并不爱他  所以呢  成就了我的美事
she didn't love him, which incidentally worked out pretty well for me.
咱们停车场见
See you in the parking lot.
瑞秋
No, Rach!
她又再一次离开了  谁赌9点45分的
And once again she is out of here. Okay who had 9:45? Um?
知道吗  巴瑞  我不会走的
You know what Barr, I'm not gonna leave.
我大概应该走  但是我不走
I probably should, but I'm not,
因为我答应自己  至少要
see 'cause I promised myself that I would make it through
参加完一次你的婚礼
at least one of your weddings.
今晚  其实我只想要
See now, tonight, all I really wanted was
安然度过  保留一点点的
to make it though this evening with a little bit of
风度跟尊严
grace and dignity.
我想我们都同意  那是不可能的了
Well, I guess we can all agree that's not gonna happen.
我想也没什么好说的了
There's nothing really left to say
除了
except....
她的名字叫劳拉
Her name was Lola.
是个歌舞女郎
She was a showgirl.
头上装饰着黄色羽毛
With yellow feathers, feathers in her hair,
裙子开放而性感  她会
and a dress cut down to there. She would...
跳梅伦格舞
Marenge,
跳梅伦格舞  谢谢你  亲爱的
...marenge, thank you honey,
还会跳恰恰
and do the cha-cha.
在她努力成为一个明星的那段日子里
And while she liked to be a star,
托尼为了她一直在酒吧工作
Tony always tended bar.
等等  大家一起来
At the, wait, wait, everybody..
大家一起来
Everybody!
在古巴  古巴卡巴那
At the Copa, Copa Cabana
哈瓦那北方最繁华的地方
The hottest spot north of Havana.
在古巴  古巴卡巴那
At the Copa, Coo-pa Ca-ban-a,
音乐与时髦永享激情
music and fashion were always the passion,
在古巴...
at the Copa....
好吧  我愿意
Okay, I'll do it.
你愿意什么
You'll do what?
如果必须有孩子才能和你在一起  那就有吧
If kids is what I takes to be with you then kids it is.
天啊
Oh my God!
如果必须的话  我就再来一次
If I have to I'll, I'll do all again ,
我会四点起来喂奶
I'll do the 4 o'clock feeding thing,
我会参加家长会  我会当足球队的教练
I'll go to the P.T.A. meetings, I'll coach the soccer team.
真的
Really?
对  如果必须的话
Yeah, if I have to.
莫妮卡
Monica,
我不想失去你
I don't wanna lose you,
所以如果我必须得重来一次  我还是会的
so if I have to do it all over again, then I will.
你真是我遇见过的最棒的男人
You're the most wonderful man.
如果你没说
And if you hadn't of said
"如果必须的话"  说了那么多遍
'if I have to' like seventeen times,
那么我会说  "好吧  咱们生吧"
then I'd be saying 'okay, let's do it.'
但是你不会
But you're not.
天啊
Oh my God,
真不敢相信我就要这么说了
I can't believe what I'm getting ready to say.
我想要一个孩子
I wanna have a baby,
但我不想跟一个
but I don't wanna have one
并不是真的想要孩子的人一起生
with someone who doesn't really wanna have one.
天啊
God.
我爱你
I love you.
我知道
I know you do.
我也爱你
Me too.
现在呢
So what now?
现在我们就只能一直跳下去了
I guess we just keep dancing.
她在哪里  她在哪里
Where is she, Where is she?
我有个问题  她在哪里
Oh, hey, I have a question, where is she?
钱德勒  你放心吧  她会来的
Chandler, relax, Chandler, she'll be here.
她来了
Ooh, oh, oh, that's her.
对  因为人生真美好
Yeah, 'cause life's just that kind.
钱德勒  你不能盯着门看
Chandler, you gotta stop staring at the door.
这就像心急水不开一样  如果你一直盯着
It's like a watched pot, you know if you keep looking at it
那扇门就永远不会开的
then the door is to, never gonna boil.
我认为你必须试着不去...
I think what you have to do is try not to...
我的天
Oh my God!
Oh.....My.....God!!
我的天
好吧  我一直觉得好对不起你
All right I've been feeling incredibly guilty about this,
因为我想当个好朋友
because I wanna be a good friend,
该死  我是个好朋友
and dammit I am a good friend.
所以  闭嘴并且闭上眼睛
So just, just shut up and close your eyes.
你真是好朋友
You are a good friend,
试镜是今天早上  我出局了
'course the audition was this morning, and I didn't get it.
但是你吻技真不错
But that was a hell of a kiss.
瑞秋是个很幸运的女孩
Rachel is a very lucky girl.